# HIMANSHI SAHU

## QA TEST ENGINEER





+91-8097415371

✓ himanshisahuhs@gmail.com

Panvel, Navi Mumbai

# SKILLS

Software Testing: Black-box
Testing, White-box Testing,
Regression Testing, Functional
Testing, UAT

Frontend Development: React.js,
JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,
Tailwind CSS

Backend & Database: MySQL

Automation & Programming: Basic
Java, Selenium WebDriver

# EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

Shri Balaji Institute of Technology & Mgmt., Betul. (RGPV University, Bhopal)

2011 - 2015

## PROFILE

I have 4 years of experience in software testing, specializing in manual testing. My passion for technology has led me to explore development. I have completed an advanced software testing course and am currently learning MERN stack development to build modern and efficient web applications.

## EXPERIENCE

#### QUALITY AND ASSURANCE TESTER

Xanax Technologies

3rd Oct 2022 to 15th oct-2023

- Requirements analysis
- Creation of test cases, checklists and test scenarios.
- Reviewing test cases, updating old ones.
- Performing various testing like regression testing, sanity testing, integration testing, user acceptance testing.
- Producing test reports Communication with the team.
- Automation of some routine tasks for making the work faster using Java+Selenium.

#### SOFTWARE TESTER

ShujaBITS Infotech Solutions Private Limited

11th Jan 2022 to 30th June-2022

- Requirements analysis.
- Creation of test cases, test plan and test scenarios.
- · Reviewing test cases, updating old ones.
- Communication with the team

### **SOFTWARE TESTER**

Codestrela Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

1st Jan 2019 to 31st Dec-2021

- Requirements analysis.
- Creation of test cases, test plan and test scenarios.
- Documentation work
- · Mobile Testing.